{
    "subject": "Abel_Gance",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Un_drame_au_ch\u00e2teau_d'Acre",
    "human_readable": "Abel Gance created Un drame au ch\u00e2teau d'Acre.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8951386213302612,
            "question": "Who created the film 'Un drame au ch\u00e2teau d'Acre'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7295787334442139,
            "question": "What are some themes explored in 'Un drame au ch\u00e2teau d'Acre'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6630902290344238,
            "question": "How was 'Un drame au ch\u00e2teau d'Acre' received by audiences at the time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6591596603393555,
            "question": "Where might 'Un drame au ch\u00e2teau d'Acre' be set?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.568120002746582,
            "question": "What kind of story does 'Un drame au ch\u00e2teau d'Acre' tell?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5490638613700867,
            "question": "Has 'Un drame au ch\u00e2teau d'Acre' had any lasting cultural impact?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42044878005981445,
            "question": "What is the title of the film created by Abel Gance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.355173796415329,
            "question": "What era was Abel Gance working in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30183103680610657,
            "question": "Is Abel Gance known for any other films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19648253917694092,
            "question": "What cinematic techniques did Abel Gance use in his films?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Abel Gance created Un drame au ch\u00e2teau d'Acre.",
            "html": "yago_4167_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Abel Gance known for any other films?",
            "html": "yago_4167_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What era was Abel Gance working in?",
            "html": "yago_4167_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the title of the film created by Abel Gance?",
            "html": "yago_4167_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4167_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4167_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4167_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4167_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4167_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4167_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4167_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4167_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4167_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4167_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Abel Gance created Un drame au ch\u00e2teau d'Acre.\" Specifically, the document `5.txt` mentions this film and notes that it was completed in five days for 5000 francs. Additionally, `20.txt` refers to this as one of Abel Gance's early films."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}